{ "questions": 
  [
    {
      "question" : "What's the name of our CEO?",
      "answer" : "Melissa",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Lisa","Thomas","Laura"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's our favourite color?",
      "answer" : "Green",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Red","Black","Pink"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "Where are our headquarters?",
      "answer" : "Nuremberg",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Prague","London","Paris"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's our official chatting tool?",
      "answer" : "Slack",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["IRC","Messenger","Rocket Chat"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's our favourite pet?",
      "answer" : "Chameleon",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Cat","Dog","Lizard"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "Do we allow remote working?",
      "answer" : "Yes",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["No","Only on Fridays","Only in Germany"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's the last released version of the SUSE Linux Enterprise Server?",
      "answer" : "15 SP4",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["15 SP2","12 SP4","13 SP7"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's the name of openSUSE rolling release?",
      "answer" : "Tumbleweed",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Tumblewide","Leap","SLES"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "When was released the first version of SUSE (S.u.S.E. Linux 4.2)?",
      "answer" : "1996",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["1988","1992","2005"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "How do we call our pet?",
      "answer" : "Geeko",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Greeny","Susy","Leap"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is bug bsc#547233 about?",
      "answer" : "Cold fusion",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Time travel","SUSE Manager","SLE"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What's short name of the annual SUSE Conference?",
      "answer" : "SUSECon",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["GreenCon","SUSEConf","Geekcon"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "'Smarter innovation that puts you back in control' refers to",
      "answer" : "SUSE",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Brexit","Tante Suzie","Sushi"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What manages your network interfaces on SLES?",
      "answer" : "Wicked",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Vicious","Black Magic","Network Ballader"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "Our slogan is: We adapt, you ...",
      "answer" : "succeed",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["listen","have coffee","applaude"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What tool does SLES use to update software from online?",
      "answer" : "zypper",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["yum","apt-get","cron"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "S.u.S.E. was abreviation for System and Software ...",
      "answer" : "Development",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Enhancement","Analysis","Training"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "On what distribution was S.u.S.E based until version 4.2?",
      "answer" : "Slackware",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Red Hat","Debian","Knoppix"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is the name of the SUSE tool used to build images?",
      "answer" : "Kiwi",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Lime","Lemon","Mango"]
    },
    {
      "question" : "In which year was SUSE founded?",
      "answer" : "1992",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["1996","1989","2001"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "In which city was SUSE founded?",
      "answer" : "Fuerth",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["New York","Nuremberg","Moscow"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "Which one is NOT a SUSE value?",
      "answer" : "We take it easy",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["We are SUSE","We are collaborative","We are empowered and accountable"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "Which one is NOT a SUSE value?",
      "answer" : "We do what we need to do",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["We are passionate about customers","We are respectful and inclusive","We are trustworthy and act with integrity"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "How many employees does SUSE vaguely have?",
      "answer" : "2000",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["1100","750","9500"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "What means SLE?",
      "answer" : "SUSE Linux Enterprise",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["SUSE Linux Extreme","SUSE Linux Extra","SUSE Linux Elysium"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "How long does SUSE support SLES?",
      "answer" : "10+3 years",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["at least 3 years","as long as there are paying customers","8 years"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "Which company did SUSE acquire recently?",
      "answer" : "Rancher Labs",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["Red Hat","Novell","Walmart"]
    },
   {
      "question" : "What is K3S?",
      "answer" : "A Kubernetes distribution",
      "wrongAnswers" : ["A Kerberos service","A Kettle Stand","A cloud company"]
    }
  ]
}
